24小时
第三季  第18集
前情提要
阿尔梅达
Almeida.
托尼 是我 盖尔死了
Tony, it's me, Gale is dead.
他死的时候非常痛苦
He was suffering so badly.
谁都不该承受那种痛苦
No one should have to go through what he did.
楼上还有很多孩子
There are children upstairs
他们也将这么痛苦的死去
who are going to die in agony.
米歇尔 非常不幸 我们也帮不了他们
Michelle, unfortunately, there is nothing we can do for them right now.
其实 可以
Actually, there is.
给那些酒店的人准备的自杀胶囊
The suicide capsules, for the people down at the hotel.
这违反规定
It's against every regulation in the book.
对
Yeah.
就这么办吧
Do it.
趴下!
Get down!
那些关于桑德斯的资料
The Saunders' computer file.
存在哪个服务器上?
What server did you store it on?
A5
A5.
蔡斯 有炸弹
Chase, we got a bomb.
还有多少时间?
How much time?
没了
None.
我拿到了 走 快走!
I got it. Go, go!
查佩尔
Chappelle.
瑞恩 我是杰克 几乎整个军情6处都被毁了
Ryan, it's Jack, almost the entire MI6 office has just been wiped out.
什么?
What?
桑德斯试图毁掉的东西中
One of the things that Saunders was trying to destroy
有军情6处收集的关于他的资料
was all the information that MI6 had gathered on him.
我想办法抢回了存储这些资料的硬盘
I managed to retrieve the hard drive.
你有什么发现吗?
Have you get anything yet?
我正试图追踪资金流向
I am trying to follow the money trail.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
给你下一个任务
To give you your next assignment.
有个叫瑞恩·查佩尔的 反恐组的地区主管
There is a man named Ryan Chappelle, regional director of CTU.
我要他死
I want him killed.
这不可能
It's out of the question.
在你决定之前
Before you decide,
最好去钱德勒 广场酒店参观一下
you might want to drop by the Chandler Plaza Hotel,
看看都发生了什么
take a good look at what's happening.
再想象一下全国各地发生同样的事
Then imaging the same event taking place at hundreds of locations all over the country.
你疯了
You are insane.
以下事件发生于6点至7点之间
The following takes place between 6:00 am and 7:00 am.
总统办公室也不能凌驾于法律之上
This office isn't above the law.
我怎能堂而皇之的草菅人命?
How can I justify authorizing the murder of an innocent man?
大卫 这是一场战争
David, we're fighting a war.
瑞恩·查佩尔不是普通平民 他应该能理解
Ryan Chappelle is not a civilian.
我还是不能下令杀了他
I still can't order him to be killed.
不这么做又能怎么办?
So what's the alternative?
大卫 我知道这样很极端
Yes, David, I know it's extreme.
但这是我们唯一的出路
I realize that, but it's the only move we have here.
看看钱德勒 广场酒店都发生了什么
Look at what's happening right now down at the Chandler Plaza.
如果你不照他说的做 这个桑德斯会用病毒
This man Saunders has proven that he will use this virus
害死更多的人
to inflict mass casualties if you don't do what he says.
我还要被桑德斯操纵多久?
How long am I supposed to let Saunders dictate my actions?
他还要拿全国人的安危要挟我多久?
How long do I allow him to hold this country hostage?
一直到我们抓到他
Until we catch him.
如果抓不到呢?
And if we don't?
会抓到的
We will.
但在那之前 只能牺牲查佩尔
But until we do, your only option is to sacrifice Chappelle.
我把从军情6处取来的硬盘交给了信息研究室
I handed the hard drive from MI6 over to the IT lab.
他们正在整理资料
They are sorting through the data now.
伦敦方面想要你说明一下军情6处发生了什么
London wants you to debrief them on what went down with MI6.
有关于桑德斯的重大发现吗?
Are we any closer to finding Saunders?
他用一部扰频的手机与总统联系
He is using a scrambler phone to contact the President.
亚当说要追查他的位置大概要24个小时
Adam says it could take up to 24 hours to trace his location.
这是唯一的线索吗?
Is that the only search protocol we have got going?
桑德斯通过洛杉矶某地的服务器转帐给阿马多尔
Saunders transferred money to Amador using a server somewhere in Los Angeles.
我正试着追踪阿马多尔的资金流向看看能否倒查到桑德斯那里
I am trying follow Amador's money trail to see if it leads back to Saunders.
但你还是一无所获
But you haven't turned up anything yet.
对
No.
我们从唐人街的Go会所没收的电脑没什么价值
The computer we confiscated from the Go club in Chinatown is a dead end.
我正准备查一下桑德斯海外帐户的交易记录
I am trying to back trace payments made to Saunders' offshore accounts.
好的
Ok, fine.
杰克 总统办公室的电话
Jack, the President's office is holding for you.
让他们把电话转接到这个房间
Have them transfer the call down here.
他想和你单独谈谈
He asked to speak to you in private.
他在7号线
He's on the line at station seven.
失陪
Excuse me.
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
鲍尔探员 请稍候
Agent Bauer, please hold for the President.
总统先生 已接通杰克·鲍尔
Mr President, I have Jack Bauer for you.
杰克.
Jack
总统先生
Mr President.
没人在你身边?
Are you alone right now?
对
Yes, sir.
桑德斯几分钟前给我打了电话 提出了新的要求
Saunders called me a few minutes ago. He has made another demand.
是什么?
What is it?
这很难办 杰克
This is a hard one, Jack.
我有话直说了
So I am going to be as direct as I can be.
他要瑞恩·查佩尔的命
He wants Ryan Chappelle dead.
什 什么 我不明白
I, I am sorry. I don't understand.
他要我们把他的尸体送到市区火车站的主轨旁边
He wants his body delivered to the train yard downtown.
为什么桑德斯想要查佩尔的命?
Why would Saunders want Chappelle dead?
我不知道 他也不会告诉我
I don't know. He wouldn't give me a reason.
他的态度很强硬 如果不能如他所愿 后果不堪设想
But he was emphatic about the consequences if his demand wasn't met.
杰克,
Jack
我感觉正在做一件无法挽回的事
I feel as though I'm crossing a line that I will never be able to step back from.
这么说你已经决定了?
So, then you have made your decision. Sir?
除非你能想出个万全之策
Unless you can suggest a way to handle this.
最后期限是什么时候?
What time is this supposed to happen?
7点
7:00.
也许我能在那之前找到桑德斯
Maybe I can find Saunders before then.
不到一个小时了
That's in less than an hour.
我明白
Yes, I know, sir.
我得抓紧了
I should get going.
杰克
Jack.
很抱歉我把包袱丢给你 但除了你我不知道该给谁打电话
I am sorry to put this on you, but I didn't know who else to call.
我明白 先生
I understand, sir.
我一会打给你
I'll get back to you.
克萝伊
Chloe.
你们在怎么查桑德斯?
What are you doing right now to help find Saunders?
事实上 我们正在把数据上传总部
Actually, we are relaying our data streams to division.
为什么?
Why are you sending them there?
那里现在是信息中心
Well, they're the hub now.
查佩尔让他们给我们收集信息
Chappelle has them gathering information for us.
国防部 军情6处
DOD, MI6.
别管这些了
No, forget about that.
我要你先放下这些 现在就开始调查
I want you to mirror everything they are doing and start your search from here.
好 调查什么?
Ok, what kind of search?
我们调查桑德斯最多的资料是什么?
What's the largest base of knowledge we have on Saunders?
金融方面
Financial.
好 顺着这个查
Ok, follow the bank trails.
我向查佩尔汇报一下
I will have to clear it with Chappelle.
不 不行
No, you can't do that.
他给我的任务 他职位比你高 杰克
Well, he gave the order. He outranks you, Jack.
克萝伊 你得按我说的做 好吗?
Chloe, you are gonna do what I asked you, ok?
还有别让查佩尔知道 明白吗?
And you are not gonna let Chappelle know, you got it?
不 我不明白 他对我已经一肚子火了 我不想再把他惹毛了
No, I don't got it. He's mad at me for, like 12 things. I am not ganna add that to the list.
克萝伊
Chloe.
克萝伊 若非紧急关头我不会让你这么做
Chloe, I wouldn't ask you to do it like this if it wasn't very important.
请帮我这个忙
Ok, so, please just do this for me.
好吧
Fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
酒店几乎三分之一的人都已出现病症 情况还在恶化
Nearly a third of the people in this hotel are symptomatic, and it's getting worse every minute.
他们有权结束自己生命
They should have the choice to end their own lives.
胶囊很快会送到
The capsules should be there soon.
托尼?
Tony?
嗯
Yeah.
我知道你我都在尽量回避这个话题 但...
I realize we have both been talking around this, but...
如果我的检测结果是已感染...
If my test comes back positive...
米歇尔 别这么想
Michelle, don't go there.
宝贝 我们都清楚我活下去的希望不大了
Sweetheart, we both know my chances of survival are low.
还有希望 你还有希望
You still have a chance, and while there's still a chance,
我不想再提这个了
I don't want to talk about this.
好 只是...
Ok, just...
不管怎样 我想要你知道
no matter what, I just want you to know,
过去的三年是我一生中最美好的时光
the last 3 years have been the best years of my life.
我应该在你身边的
I should be there with you.
你已经在了
You are.
不 这不一样
No, it's not the same.
你现在能为我做的
The best thing you can do for me right now
就是确保那些胶囊送到这里
is to make sure those capsules get here.
我会尽力
I will do my best.
我相信
I know you will.
托尼 我得和你谈谈
Tony, I need to speak to you.
米歇尔?
Michelle?
对
Yeah
她拿到检测报告了吗?
Did she get the test results back yet?
没 还要等一个小时
No, they won't have them back for another hour yet.
怎么了?
What's going on?
你知不知道桑德斯和查佩尔过去是否有过接触 他们之间有没有什么联系?
Do you know if Saunders and Chappelle had any history, if their paths had ever crossed?
我不清楚
Not that I am aware of.
你在找什么样的联系?
What kind of connection are you looking for?
让桑德斯对查佩尔起杀心的联系
The kind that would make Saunders want Chappelle killed.
因为他已经要总统这么做了
Because that's exactly what he just ordered the President to do.
在7点之前 他要看到瑞恩·查佩尔的尸体
By 7:00 a.m., he wants Ryan Chappelle dead.
为什么?
Why?
这正是我想知道的
That's what I am trying to figure out.
总统让你来解决
And the President put this on you.
我不知道如果7点以前还找不到桑德斯该怎么办
I don't know what I am going to do if we don't find Saunders by 7:00.
你告诉瑞恩了吗?
Have you told Ryan about this?
没还没有
No, not yet.
在那之前我得先改一下他的安全密码
I should probably change his security clearance before you do.
你认为他会逃跑?
You really think he is a flight risk?
我们不能冒险
We can't take a chance right now.
必须找到桑德斯
We have to find Saunders.
我去让查佩尔把他的资料都传给克萝伊
I will get Chappelle to send all his data over to Chloe.
你再尽量分些人手和她一起整理这些资料
You prepare her and whoever else you can spare to sort through it.
他们也许想知道怎么回事
They are gonna want to know what's going on.
他们没必要知道这么清楚
They don't need to know.
我来办吧
I will take care of it.
谢谢
Thank you.
-克萝伊  -请讲
-Chloe.  -Yeah.
我要你暂时放下手上的工作
I need you to put all your protocols on hold for at least an hour.
明白
Got it.
总统和你说了些什么?
What did the President want to talk to you about?
关于你
You.
我?
Me?
我的事?
What about me?
瑞恩 来
Ryan, come with me.
先坐下
Just take a seat.
怎么了 杰克?
What's going on here, Jack?
桑德斯打电话来提了新的要求
Saunders called in with another demand.
他又想要干什么?
What does he want now?
杰克
Jack.
他要你的命
He wants you killed.
不是在开玩笑吧?
Is this some kind of a joke?
不是 瑞恩
It's no joke, Ryan.
他威胁说如果7点以前我们不把你的尸体送到指定位置 他就释放病毒
He's threatened to release the virus into the main population unless we deliver your body by 7:00 a.m.
什么 帕默尔决定妥协了?
What, did Palmer actually go along with this?
我的上帝 杰克
My god, Jack.
他已证明会继续放毒 总统别无选择
He has proven he will use the virus. The President had no choice.
那总统让你来取我的命?
So he sent you to kill me?
假如7点之前找不到桑德斯
Not if we can find Saunders before 7:00 a.m.
哦 太好了 时间多着呢 不是吗?
Oh, great, that gives us a lot of time, doesn't it?
我 我不明白 为什么是我?
I, I don't understand this, why me?
我们也不知道
We don't know.
瑞恩 你得仔细想想
Ryan, I need you to think real hard.
你和桑德斯有没有过我们都不知道的过去?
Do you have any past connection with Saunders that we don't know about?
没有
No.
我今天才第一次听说斯蒂芬 桑德斯这个名字
The first time I heard the name Stephen Saunders was today.
你一直在调查资金动向 也许是这个原因
The money transactions that you have been investigating that's what must have triggered this.
我还没追查到桑德斯
I haven't had the chance to trace them to Saunders yet.
事实上 他想要你的命
The fact that he wants you dead.
这证明你接着查下去肯定能找到他
That proves that they lead back to him.
你指望在7点之前能弄明白?
And you expect to figure this out by 7:00?
尽快找到桑德斯是你唯一的活路
Finding Saunders in time is the only way to keep you alive.
我会想尽一切办法
And I will use everything in my disposal to do that.
瑞恩 我需要你的帮助
Ryan, I need your help.
我要你所有的文件 把它们交给克萝伊 让她接着查
I need all your files, and I mean everything sent over to Chloe's desk so she can start going through it.
很抱歉 瑞恩
I am sorry, Ryan.
让我们找出这个混蛋
Let's find this guy.
你发现什么了 瑞恩?
What have you got, Ryan?
我找到了桑德斯在开曼s银行的海外帐户
I found Saunders' offshore bank account in the Caymans.
我从银行的网络进入了他的帐户 但被加密了
I was able to access his account information off their network, but it's encrypted.
又是个难题
Another brick wall.
全交给克萝伊吧
Just send it over to Chloe's desk.
她也许能破解密码
If anyone can break the encryption, she can.
来不及了
Not in the time that we have.
未必 瑞恩
You don't know that, Ryan.
必须现在 杰克 现在
It has to be now, Jack, now.
就是这样
This is it.
你还不明白吗?
Don't you understand?
你当然一清二楚
Of course you understand.
你是来杀我的
You are the one who is going to kill me.
我们在尽最大努力
We are doing everything we can.
你有没有想过根本与这这帐户不相干?
Don't you realize the possibility that this might not even be relevant?
桑德斯知道杀了我 调查也不会中止
Saunders knows if he kills me, it doesn't kill the investigation.
也许我知道别的什么事他才想杀我
He might want me dead for something else I know,
一些和我暂时还不知道的事
something I haven't made a connection with yet.
那就仔细想想 瑞恩 仔细想想
Well, then think, Ryan, think.
别向那个混蛋投降
But don't give in to this bastard.
我们齐心协力 一定能找到他 好吗?
With all of us working together, we are going to find this guy, ok?
把加密的帐号交给克萝伊处理 我来给她解释 快
Send the encrypted account over to Chloe's desk, I will explain it to her. Come on.
克萝伊 瑞恩有些资料发给你
Chloe, Ryan is forwarding a file to you.
求求你 让我给我妻子打个电话
Please let me, let me call my wife.
对不起 我们还得继续封锁所有消息 以防造成恐慌
I am sorry, we are still under orders to keep what's going on secret, so we don't create panic.
我知道 我什么也不说 你可以派人监听
Yeah, I won't tell her anything, and your people can listen in.
这是总统直接下达的命令
That order comes directly from the President.
我已经倾尽所能帮你了 求求你
I have done everything I can do to help you, please.
我只想 我只想听听她的声音 求你了
I just want, I just want to hear her voice, please.
对不起
I'm sorry.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
请大家注意
Can I have your attention, please.
我接下来要说的你们也许不愿意听
What I'm about to tell you will be difficult to hear,
但这很重要 掌握所有信息你们才能作自己的决定
but it's important that you have all the information so you can each make your own decision.
首先 我要你们知道...
First, I want all of you to know that ...
一旦出现感染的病症
once symptoms of infection appear,
就无法治愈
there is no chance of recovery.
随着病毒的深入 它会攻击人体器官和主要血管
As the virus progresses, it attacks the body's organs and major blood vessels.
极其痛苦
This process is extremely painful.
在6小时内会致人死亡
The estimated time of death is within 6 hours.
我尽可能直话直说是因为
I am telling you all of this as directly as possible because
我们能给你们另一种选择
we can offer each of you an alternative
有一些药丸
Some pills you can take
服下后你们会平静的死去
that will basically make you feel like you are going to sleep.
由你们自己决定何时
It will be up to each one of you to decide when,
还有是否使用这些药丸
and if you want to use these drugs.
这些药物很快会被送到
They will be available shortly.
谢谢
Thank you.
米歇尔 有麻烦了
Michelle, we have a situation.
一个女人说她找不到和她一起来的男人了
A woman came forward to tell us she can't find the man she was here with.
她已经几个小时没看到他了
She hasn't seen him for a few hours.
你确定不在隔离区?
Are you sure he is not in isolation?
是 我们带她看了
Yeah, we let her look.
他叫什么?
What's his name?
这也是个问题 她说她不知道
That's part of the problem. She claims she doesn't know.
我是联邦探员米歇尔·德斯勒
I am agent Michelle Dessler.
我叫凯西 全名凯西·麦卡特尼
I am Kathy, Kathy McCartney.
你也知道现在控制住所有感染的人有多重要
You realize how important it is that we account for everyone who may have been infected.
对 我正是为此而来
Yes, that's why I came forward.
你必须诚实
We need you to be completely honest.
我没撒谎
I am.
我只知道他叫比尔 我甚至不知道是不是真名
All I know is that his name is Bill, and I am not even sure if that's real.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我们今天在山上的一家具乐部相识
We met tonight at a club on hill,
我们很来电 所以到这儿来了
and we really connected, so we decided to come here.
谁定的房间?
Who booked the room?
是我
I did.
你上次见到他是什么时候?
Do you remember the last time you saw him?
我们在屋里睡着了
Oh, we fell asleep together in the room,
后来火警的声音吵醒了我们 他就出去了
and when the fire alarm woke me up, he was gone.
你有没有印象几点睡的?
Do you remember what time you fell asleep?
我记得很清楚 我看了下表 4点02分
I know exactly, I looked at the clock., it was 4:02.
呆在这
Stay here, please.
如果她没记错时间
If she is right about the time,
病毒释放的时候 那男子还在酒店内
then this man was in the hotel when the virus was released
在完全隔离后 他离开了酒店
and he got out of the building before it was completely locked down.
有没有可能他躲在酒店的某个角落?
Is it possible he is hiding somewhere in the hotel?
不 不
No, no.
我们把所有人都控制在客房里
We have accounted for everyone in the guest rooms,
还用红外线扫描了所有公共区域
and we have done an infrared sweep of all the public areas.
艾德 叫现场调查组到她房间去 取指纹
Ed, get a forensic team up to her room, dust for prints.
那可能有成百上千的指纹
There will be dozens of people's prints in there.
执行命令
Just do it.
我是米勒探员 我们需要现场勘查小组
This is agent Miller. We need a forensic team right now.
凯西 你得跟我来
Kathy, I need you to come with me.
为什么?
Why?
你得告诉我所有那个比尔可能碰过的地方
You need to show me every surface that Bill may have touched.
快
Come on.
多谢
Thanks.
克萝伊需要更强的分析网络
Chloe needs as much processing power as she can get.
我要你再给她一个端口
I need you to open up another socket in the network for her.
他怎么样了?
How's he going?
他吓坏了
He's scared.
蔡斯已经集合了一支作战队
All right, Chase has a strike team assembled.
一旦发现桑德斯的行踪 他们随时可以出发
They're ready to go as soon as we get a location on Saunders.
另外我从空中作战部那给你安排了一架直升机
Also, I ordered you a helicopter from air tactical.
火车站那里交通繁忙
Train yard has all the way across town.
我们不能把时间浪费在交通上
We can't afford to be slowed down by rush hour traffic.
好的
Ok, good.
我马上给克萝伊分配端口
I will get the socket open for Chloe.
非常感谢
Thanks a lot.
杰克 银行的密码很复杂 我们准备暴力破解
Jack, the bank used deep encryption. We are going to have to use a password crack.
需要多少时间?
How long is that going to take?
大概90分钟
It'll take as long as 90 minutes.
来不及了
We don't have that much time.
我已经尽力了 或许你应该告诉我为什么这个如此重要
I am doing the best I can. Maybe it would help if you told us why this is overriding other protocols.
你只需要知道我现在就要解密这些文件
The only thing you need to know is I need these files decrypted now.
我正竭尽所能 你的话丝毫不能鼓舞士气
I am doing my very best. Your tone of voice is not exactly a morale booster.
克萝伊 按我所的做
Chloe, please just do it.
克萝伊 我来帮你 我们并联处理
Chloe, let me help, we can parallel process.
好 好主意
Ok, good idea.
哦 瑞恩
Oh, Ryan.
很抱歉 查佩尔先生 你不能离开
I am sorry, Mr Chappelle. We are not allowed to let you leave.
什么?
What?
请回到反恐组 先生
Please return to CTU, sir.
你以为你在和谁...
Who the hell do you think...
我们奉命行事
We have orders.
谁?
From who?
我是地区主管 我撤销所有你接到的命令
I am regional director, I countermand any order you have been given.
瑞恩
Ryan.
到底怎么了杰克?
What the hell's going on here, Jack?
为什么我不能离开这栋大厦?
Why aren't I being allowed to leave the building?
你以为我要逃?
You think I am trying to run?
我只是想出去抽根烟
I am going outside to smoke a cigarette.
我不会拿上百万条人命换我一条活路
I wouldn't condemn millions of people to death so I could live.
给我看看你的烟
Let me see the cigarettes.
他们会护送你去留滞室
These men will escort you back to holding.
不行
I don't think so.
我不是在征求你的意见 瑞恩
I am not asking, Ryan.
我有国家总统授予我的权力
Under the authority given to me by the President of the United States,
我命令你
I am ordering you.
托尼 是我 有麻烦了
Tony, it's me. We have a problem.
刚才确定有一名男子接触病毒后离开了酒店
We just determined a man who was exposed to the virus got out of the hotel
该死的 怎么会这样?
Son of a bitch. How'd that happen?
他是在增强警戒之前逃出去的
He must have slipped out right before we reinforced the perimeter.
好像他并不知道自己已接触病毒
It's likely he had no idea he'd been exposed.
有没有通知卫生署?
Have you notified Health Services?
有 他们已经知道了
Yeah, they are aware of the situation.
问题是 我们不知道他在哪
The problem is, we don't know who he is.
他没有登记过
He wasn't a registered guest.
他到酒店干什么去的?
What was he doing inside the hotel?
一夜情
Having a one night stand.
和他一夜风流的女人来告诉我们情况
The woman he was with came forward.
监控录像有没有发现?
Any sign of him on the surveillance cameras?
前台这里没有 似乎没人看到他进出
Nothing at the front desk, and no one seems to have seen him come or go.
那怎么办?
What are we doing to find him?
最大希望是提取指纹核对了
Our best shot to ID him is off prints.
我们已经从显要处提取了很多
We have already pulled dozens from all the obvious surfaces,
灯具开关 洗浴间等
light switches bathroom fixtures.
好的 听着 把这些指纹传过来 我们来查
All right, look, send the prints over to us, we will work them up.
看看从那女人那里还能发现什么
See what else you can find off this woman.
明白
Got it.
-我记得的就这么多了  -好
-It's all I can remember.  -OK.
对不起我帮不了你们
I am sorry I can't be more helpful.
不 你已经帮了我们很多
No, you are doing great.
你再回想一遍
Let's just go over this one more time.
你们两个进入房间...
The two of you came into the room...
我拿着钥匙
I had the key,
是我开的门
so I am the one who opened the door.
我们没开灯
We didn't turn the lights on or off.
他有没有去放下窗帘?
Did he go over to the window draw the blinds?
没有 我们立刻开始接吻
No, we just started kissing right away.
你站在哪里?
Where were you standing?
在这 床边
I was here, by the bed.
然后呢?
And then what happened?
他开始脱我的衣服
He started taking my clothes off.
你现在穿的?
The clothes you are wearing now?
对 他脱了我的上衣 然后是裤子 然后
Yeah. He pulled my shirt over my head and then my pants and then...
我需要你的皮带
I need your belt.
米勒 查一下皮带扣
Miller, try the buckle.
像是她自己的指纹
Prints look like hers.
等一下
Hold it.
我找到了一个局部拇指纹
I got a partial thumb.
不是她的?
It's not hers?
我在核对
Checking
不是 她的拇指是反向螺旋 这个不是
No. She's got inverse swirls. This print doesn't.
把这个上传给反恐组 现在
Upload it to CTU, now.
如果不能在他病发前找到他 恐怕病毒会泛滥
If we don't find this guy before he becomes symptomatic, we might be looking at an outbreak.
你去哪了?
Where have you been?
和客户谈点事
I had a client meeting.
我不是告诉过你 太晚我就不回来了
I told you that I wouldn't come home if it went too late.
好吧
That's right.
我希望你打电话说一声 我很担心
I kind of wish you would have called.I was worried.
我不想吵醒你
I didn't want to wake you up.
杰克 有发现
Jack, I think I am getting something.
在尝试了最后一组密码后
Applying the last layer of key words,
成功了 密码被破解
it worked, we cracked the decryption.
我们进入了桑德斯的银行帐号
We have access to Saunders' bank account.
查询户头 看看能不能找到地址
Go into the header, tell me what address they have got on him.
国内有很多处 有一处在洛杉矶
There is several across the country, one in Los Angels.
市区里的一个公寓 距这大概五分钟的路程
An apartment downtown, 5 minutes from here.
我们怎么确定这地址是真的?
How do we know the address is real?
每次转帐 银行都会确认地址
Every time the money is moved, the bank confirms the physical location of that call.
桑德斯45分钟前在那里转移了一笔钱
Saunders called in a transfer 45 minutes ago from that address.
我通知蔡斯
I will call Chase.
告诉他保持隐蔽
Tell him not to go in hard.
不能被桑德斯发现
Saunders can't see us coming.
干的好 太棒了
Good work. Great work.
谢谢
Thank you.
开门
Open it.
瑞恩 我们发现桑德斯了
Ryan, I think we found Saunders.
通过银行帐户?
Through his bank account?
对 45分钟前他刚在那里打过电话
Yeah. 45 minutes ago he made a call from an apartment not far from here.
蔡斯正率队过去
Chase is leading a strike team over there now.
太好了 杰克 感谢上帝
Good, Jack. Thank God.
瑞恩 我们还是得去趟火车站
Ryan, we still need to go over to the train yard.
现在?
Now?
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
我们得在最后期限之前到达那
We have to be in place before the deadline,
以防作战队失败
just in case the strike team isn't successful.
但你刚才说他45分钟前还在那
But you said they know he was there 45 minutes ago.
瑞恩 这只是备用之策
Ryan, this is just a precaution.
在抓到他之前必须这样做 你应该明白
We have to do it until we have him in custody, you know that.
直升机已经就绪 在北楼楼顶 我们得马上出发
I have got a helicopter waiting for us over in the north annex, but we should go now.
好吧 杰克
All right, Jack.
好的
Ok.
升空后再联系
We will be in touch as soon as we are airborne.
好的
All right.
查佩尔先生 总部打来电话询问你3点的简报
Mr Chappelle, division called to confirm your 3:00 briefing.
一切照常吗?
Is that still good?
对
Sure.
总统先生
Mr President.
洛杉矶时报的海伦刚给我打电话
Helen Stuppen from the LA Times just called my office.
询问钱德勒 广场酒店的病毒事件
She was asking about some kind of toxic accident at the Chandler Plaza Hotel,
以及是否与红色预警有关
and if it was connected to the red alert.
她说了些什么?
What exactly did she say?
不多 她想套我们的话
Not much. She was fishing.
总统先生 我明白有些事情 你不能说
Mr President, I appreciate that you need to keep certain things from me,
但有些事情总归瞒不住 一旦传了出去 我需要些解释
but this story will get out, and when it does, I'll need to have answers.
杰瑞是对的 大卫
Jerry is right, David.
让他也了解情况 有助于他应付媒体
And the soon we bring him into the loop, the better he can handle the press.
一种病毒在酒店的通风系统内被散播
A weaponized virus was released into that hotel's ventilation system.
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
你准备什么时候公开此事?
When will you go public with this?
只要确认病毒被控制住不再有威胁
Once we are sure that the virus has been contained and there is no longer a threat.
你确定能控制住病毒?
And how certain are you that it will be contained?
我们会尽最大的努力
We are doing everything possible.
我明白了
Yes, sir.
杰克.
Jack
托尼说你不和我们一起抓桑德斯
Tony said you are not coming with me to get Saunders.
对 你和贝克带队去
That's right. You and Baker are heading up the strike team.
等下 我不懂 桑德斯不是首要目标吗
Wait. I don't understand. Saunders is the priority.
杰克还要去市区执行别的任务
I've ordered Jack downtown to answer a few more questions.
你知道吗 瑞恩
You know what, Ryan,
你这么做是乱弹琴
all you do is put obstacles in our way.
现在有机会抓到桑德斯
We have a chance to get Saunders.
我们需要精英力量
We need our best people.
你的官僚作风让我们束手束脚
You tie us down with your bureaucratic BS.
蔡斯.
Chase
这是命令
Those are the orders.
怎么了 杰克?
What's going on, Jack?
你只管带好作战队就是
Just take care of the strike team.
他在里面吗?
Any sign that he is in there?
我看不清
I can't get a visual inside.
楼外有3个男人
We have got 3 men outside the building.
我们可以让狙击手干掉他们
We can take them out with a sniper.
不 不行
No, we can't do that.
如果失手 桑德斯就会知道我们来了
If we miss, Saunders will know we are here.
我想在近处解决他们
I want to do this up close.
这栋楼门口非常开阔 他们很远就能发现我们
The building is out in the open, they will see us coming from a block away.
这也是为什么桑德斯藏身于此
That's why Saunders picked the place.
我想不出怎么才能不惊动桑德斯
I don't see how we get to them before they can warn Saunders.
我有办法
I do.
所有飞机都已停飞
They are grounding flights from LAX.
所有行动人员都带好病毒出发了吗?
Did all the couriers get out with their vials?
纽约 华盛顿 旧金山的都已成功抵达
New York, Washington, San Francisco made it through.
他们已经快到指定位置
They are on their way.
我让去拉斯维加斯的改成开车去 他们正在路上
I rerouted Las Vegas. Our man is driving there now.
但芝加哥和克利夫兰可能到不了了
But we missed Chicago and Cleveland.
有没有大概的伤亡估计?
Did you revise the casualty projections?
当然
Of course.
告诉我数字
Just give me the number.
48小时内能造成200到500万人死亡
2 to 5 million dead within the first 48 hours.
很好
Good enough.
先生 病毒可能会蔓延到别的国家
Sir, there is a chance that the outbreak will spread beyond the Americas.
没事的 别担心
We'll be fine. Don't worry.
托尼 酒店的指纹分析结果出来了
Tony, we got results back on the fingerprint from the hotel.
什么情况?
What do you got?
如果指纹是完整的 那肯定只有一个匹配
If it had been a complete print obviously there should be only one true match.
但因为是局部的 我们找到了很多吻合的
But because it's a partial, we get results from anyone whose fingerprints match that particular guardant.
有多少?
How many potential matches we talking about?
联邦调查局档案里有大概300个
The FBI database gave us almost 300 possibilities.
好吧 把这些资料传给米歇尔 让那个女人来辨认
All right, look, upload those pictures to Michelle at the hotel. Have that woman go through them.
好 我这就去办
Ok, I am on it.
托尼 你的电话 是瑞恩·查佩尔 在3号线
Tony, Ryan Chappelle on line 3
瑞恩.
Ryan
埃德蒙兹怎么这么久?
What's taking Edmunds so long?
他有没有打电话来?
Has he even called in yet?
他已经率队到达桑德斯的藏身处
He's moving his strike team into position around Saunders' building right now.
他们还在等什么? 为什么还不行动?
What are they waiting for? Why haven't they gone in?
他们不想打草惊蛇 瑞恩
They are preparing a covert entry, Ryan.
需要点时间准备
It takes a little time.
让他们上 托尼 让他们行动
Well, get on them, Tony, get those men into that building.
瑞恩  蔡斯负责这次行动 应该让他来指挥
Ryan, Chase is running this operation on the ground, he needs to make this call.
瑞恩 蔡斯明白现在的局势
Ryan, Chase knows what's at stake here.
时机一到他们会立即行动 耐心点 放松
He's going to go in when it's safe. Just try and relax.
瑞恩 你还在听吗?
Ryan, you still there?
我在
I am here.
我把行动实时通讯转给你
All right, I am hooking you up to the real time com feed.
好
Good.
托尼 我看到火车站了
Tony, I have got a visual on the train yard.
收到
Copy that.
大厅里没人
There's no one in the lobby.
贝克和我从楼下进攻
Baker and I are moving up the stairs.
格拉夫和马丁内斯从楼上包抄
Graves and Martinez are coming down from the roof.
楼梯口的警卫已经被干掉
Guard at the top of the stairs has been taken out.
我们正向门口推进
We are proceeding down the hall.
门口有人把守
We got one man by the door.
我们得速战速决 我先冲
We have got to move fast. On my lead.
好了
Set.
确认安全
Clear.
这里没人
No one is here.
这是个中转路由器
It's a switching node.
他所有的通讯都是由此转发 该死
He's been relaying calls from this location. Damn it
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
杰克 你低估我了
You underestimate me, Jack.
桑德斯 你为何要如此?
Saunders, why are you doing this?
告诉你 你也不会明白
Even if I told you, you wouldn't understand.
不见得
Try me.
告诉你的人别费劲追踪那个中转路由器了
Tell your people not to bother tracing that relay.
我已经换了一个
I have already switched to another node.
斯蒂芬.
Stephen
一会有辆货车过来
A van will be arriving shortly.
把查佩尔的尸体留给司机
Leave Chappelle's body with the driver.
别企图跟踪他
Do not attempt to follow the van.
不按我说的做 我马上会继续投毒
If you don't follow my directions, I will release the virus immediately.
请大家注意
Can I have everyone's attention, please.
这些是刚才德斯勒探员提到的药丸
These are the drugs agent Dessler told you about earlier.
想要的上前一步
Anyone who wants to exercise this option can step forward.
米歇尔.
Michelle
查到了吗?
Did you find a match?
指纹残缺 有很多种可能
Partial thumbprint gave us a few hundred possibles, which we narrowed down to a dozen men.
我收集好了照片 麦卡特尼女士正在看
We uploaded the pictures, Ms Mccartney is looking at them now.
不是
That's not him.
不是 不是
No, no.
这个 是他
This one, I think that's him.
你肯定?
Are you sure?
对
Yeah.
我肯定
I am sure.
找到他
Find him.
你没事吧 威廉
Are you ok, William.
你在里面呆了很久了
You have been in there for awhile.
我有点不舒服
I have some kind of bug.
我给你泡杯茶吧?
You want me to make some tea?
不用 没事的
No, I am fine.
你肯定?
Are you sure?
对
Yeah.
我得去上班去了 有个会要开
Yeah, I got to go to the office. I have a staff meeting.
好吧
Ok.
考夫曼.
Kaufman
我是杰克 有没有从卫星定位系统发现我的位置?
This is Jack. Have you got satellite coverage on my position now?
还没有 我马上定位
Not yet, but I will reposition.
有一辆黑色无牌货车
There is a black van, no plates.
他们肯定有防范 但不管你用什么方法一定要跟住他
I am sure they are gonna use counter measures, but do everything you can do to follow it.
好
Ok
我们得去了 瑞恩
We have to go, Ryan.
我的腿在抖
My legs are shaking.
我明白
I have got you.
瑞恩 你还想和谁说点什么吗?
Ryan, is there anyone you want to talk to?
什么意思 说永别了?
What do you mean, to say goodbye?
想说什么都行
To say whatever you have to.
我有个兄弟 很多年没来往过了
I have a brother I haven't spoken to in years.
我没什么朋友
I don't have that many friends.
只有一些工作上的伙伴 所以 没了
Just the people at work. So, no.
没有想说话的人
There is no one.
我很抱歉 瑞恩 我们必须这么做
I am sorry, Ryan, we gotta to do this.
跪下
Get on your knees.
我们无计可施了 是吗 杰克?
There is no way around this, right, Jack?
真的没办法了吗?
We don't have any outs here?
我想不出任何办法
Not that I can see.
等等
Wait.
让我自己来吧
All right, let me do this myself.
至少给我结束自己生命的尊严
At least give me the dignity of taking my own life.
这你办得到
That's something you can do.
不 瑞恩 我不能这么做
No, Ryan, I can't do that.
你可以
Yes, you can.
之前在反恐组 你把我看管起来是对的
You were right back at CTU to put me under watch.
当时我不是出去抽烟的
I wasn't going out for a cigarette.
我想跑
I was trying to bolt.
我猜到可能会到这一步
But I know this has to happen.
我不能冒险
I can't take that chance.
我向你保证 杰克
I am giving you my word, Jack
我不会跑的 我发誓
I won't run, I swear.
说我不怕是不可能的 但我不会跑的
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't scared,but I am not gonna run.
为了求生让那么多人因我而死 我也会良心难安
I couldn't live with myself knowing I was responsible for the deaths of all those people.
你得相信我
You got to believe me.
我做不到 不行
I can't, I can't.
好吧
It's alright.
很抱歉 我们辜负了你 瑞恩
I am sorry we let you down, Ryan.
上帝宽恕我
God forgive me.